Guide to the Mix Collection, 1970-2014 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS.143
Fales Library and Special Collections
- ACCRETION 2009 - Series XXII: 2006, 246365
  - Subseries G: Media, 246368
    - The Arousing Adventures of Sailor Boy, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1939; 246393 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1939)
      Director: Bisch, Jenny
      Distributor: Winnipeg Film Group
    - CANDY: Super8 Shorts [1] -- En-Wrapped [2] -- Sugah Lips [3] -- Raining Candy [4] -- Swedish Fish [5] -- Bottoms Up [6] -- Untitled [7] -- Dirty Sweets [8] -- Candy Corn Girl [9] -- Caked [10] -- Candy Boyfriend, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1940; 246394 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1940)
      Old number: 06-209; 06-210; 06-211; 06-212; 06-213; 06-214; 06-215; 06-216; 06-217; 06-218
      Director: Hanson, Anne; Riibe, Leigh; Reynolds, Sarah; Dishman, Tracy; Schaffer, Kirsten; Park, Aaron; Marsak, Lindsay; Weakland, Sean; Carlton, Wendy Jo; Plourde, Jason
      Distributor: 2001 Seattle Lesbian & Gay Film Festival
      TRT: 00:33:20
    - Lucky 7: Super8 Films [1] -- Rainier & Cigarettes [2] -- Lucky 13 [3] -- Fast 'n' Lucky [4] -- Fishing [5] -- I Wonder [6] -- Tough Luck [7] -- My Hands [8] -- Are You The Lucky One? [9] -- Lucky Lefty [10] -- Flock of Seagulls, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1941; 246395 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1941)
      Old number: 06-219; 06-220; 06-221; 06-222; 06-223; 06-224; 06-225; 06-226; 06-227; 06-228; 06-229
      Director: Costa, Kara; Fagereng, Liev; Romano, Shannon; Baroch, Patrick; Isis Youth Group; Granada, A.J.; Garcia, Xui; Roach, Tanzania; Kennedy, Stephen; Howes, Dawn; Carlton, Wendy Jo
      TRT: 00:36:40
    - Every Wandering Cloud, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1942; 246396 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1942)
      Old number: 06-251
      TRT: 00:07:00
    - [1] -- Song of the Whoopee Wind [2] -- Beastial Comforts [3] -- Heavenly Figures [4] -- Hell Hole Hostage [5] -- The Wayward Syllabus [6] -- Holiday Hang Ups, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1943; 246397 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1943)
      Old number: 06-252; 06-253; 06-254; 06-255; 06-256; 06-257
      Year: 2005-2006
      TRT: 01:23:00
    - Pink Shirt, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1944; 246398 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1944)
      Old number: 06-267
    - Things I'll Never Say, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1945; 246399 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1945)
      Old number: 06-271
      Director: Le, Caroline
      TRT: 00:29:40
    - Angus Dei, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1946; 246400 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1946)
      Old number: 06-274
      Director: Finklestein, David
    - Draft 9, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1947; 246401 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1947)
      Old number: 06-276
      Director: Leventhal, Dani
    - Super8: Nine Worlds [1] -- Mr. McFeely's Rather Wet Package (Mercury) [2] -- Venus is a Boi Girl [3] -- Embracing Mother (Earth) [4] -- Mouth From Mars [5] -- Jupiter: AKA Little Spotty [6] -- Random (Saturn) [7] -- Uranus Can't Get a Date [8] -- Neptune [9] -- Little Pluto's Big Day, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1948; 246403 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1948)
      Old number: 06-309; 06-310; 06-311; 06-312; 06-313; 06-314; 06-315; 06-316; 06-317
      Director: Lanza, Gus; Blu, Eli Max; Richards, Apryl; Graney-Sauckle, Elliat; Isis Youthcare; Crowe, Harrison; Murphy, Brian; Ohlberg, Jason
      TRT: 00:30:00
    - [1] -- Westward Ho [2] -- 9 is a Secret, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1949; 246407 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1949)
      Old number: 06-333; 06-334
      Director: Renwick, Vanessa
      Year: 2001-2002
      TRT: 00:07:20
    - Portrait #2: Trojan, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1950; 246409 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1950)
      Old number: 06-335
    - [1] -- Bahar [2] -- Citizen Lobbyist, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1951; 246411 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1951)
      Old number: 06-365; 06-366
      Director: Karagoz, Huseyin; Watts, Tim
      Distributor: Canadian Filmmakers Distribution Center
      TRT: 02:24:00
    - [1] -- Rugburn [2] -- A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Funeral [3] -- Valley of the Chapstick [4] -- World's Worst Architecture [5] -- The Boy in the Plastic Bubble [6] -- Une Petite Morte [7] -- Game On [8] -- In Cairo [9] -- Lead Role: Father [10] -- Build [11] -- They Only Come Out At Night, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1952; 246415 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1952)
      Old number: 06-367; 06-368; 06-369; 06-370; 06-371; 06-372; 06-373; 06-374; 06-375; 06-376; 06-377
      Director: Anderson, Trevor; Barber, Max; Kennedy, Robert; Groves, Cameron; Phelan, Jamie; Cole, Keith; Caffery, John; Vaughn, RM; Raval, PJ; Atkins, Greg; McKinney, Glendon
      Year: 2004-2005
      TRT: 01:58:34
    - Tweak, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1953; 246419 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1953)
      Old number: 06-393
      Director: Schnibbe, Margie
    - Munchausen, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1954; 246421 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1954)
      Old number: 06-433
      Director: Oberbeck, Susanne
    - Spawn of Pickerel Ron, Submitted: 2006; ID: 143.1955; 246422 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1955)
      Old number: 06-434
      Director: Maryniuk, Michael